<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?mso-application progid="Excel.Sheet"?>
<Workbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office"
 xmlns:x="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel"
 xmlns:ss="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:spreadsheet"
 xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40">
 <DocumentProperties xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <LastAuthor>Quin Matteson</LastAuthor>
  <LastSaved>2016-11-02T21:36:30Z</LastSaved>
  <Version>15.00</Version>
 </DocumentProperties>
 <OfficeDocumentSettings xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office">
  <AllowPNG/>
 </OfficeDocumentSettings>
 <ExcelWorkbook xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
  <WindowHeight>13620</WindowHeight>
  <WindowWidth>28800</WindowWidth>
  <WindowTopX>0</WindowTopX>
  <WindowTopY>0</WindowTopY>
  <RefModeR1C1/>
  <ProtectStructure>False</ProtectStructure>
  <ProtectWindows>False</ProtectWindows>
 </ExcelWorkbook>
 <Styles>
  <Style ss:ID="Default" ss:Name="Normal">
   <Alignment ss:Vertical="Bottom"/>
   <Borders/>
   <Font ss:FontName="Calibri" x:Family="Swiss" ss:Size="11" ss:Color="#000000"/>
   <Interior/>
   <NumberFormat/>
   <Protection/>
  </Style>
 </Styles>
 <Worksheet ss:Name="LocStuff">
  <Table ss:ExpandedColumnCount="5" ss:ExpandedRowCount="279" x:FullColumns="1"
   x:FullRows="1" ss:DefaultRowHeight="15">
   <Column ss:Index="2" ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="510.75"/>
   <Column ss:AutoFitWidth="0" ss:Width="521.25"/>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0" ss:Height="51" ss:StyleID="s65">
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s67"><Data ss:Type="String">KEY</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s68"><Data ss:Type="String">ORIGINAL TEXT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s68"><Data ss:Type="String">TRANSLATED TEXT</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s68"><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell ss:StyleID="s68"><Data ss:Type="String">CHARACTER LIMIT</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560829</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Anders, your package arrived. Front desk. If I'm not here, the code %key% on the gate. I won't tell anyone if you don't.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Anders, your package arrived. Front desk. If I'm not here, the code's %key% on the gate. I won't tell anyone if you don't.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560831</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;The Yellow Tulip&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join us for a private celebration of TranStar's success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7:00 PM Alex Toast and Review&lt;br&gt;8:00 PM Crew Demonstration (Skye Braxton and Danielle Sho)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crew Facilities, 2nd Floor Mezzanine. </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;The Yellow Tulip&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join us for a private celebration of TranStar's success.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7:00 PM Toast and Review (Alex Yu)&lt;br&gt;8:00 PM Crew Demonstration (Skye Braxton and Danielle Sho)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Crew Facilities, 2nd Floor Mezzanine.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560889</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">REMINDER: Workers on the fabrication floor must scrub up to their elbows before entering the gowning area. NO EXCEPTIONS!  - J. Graves&lt;br&gt;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">REMINDER: Workers on the fabrication floor must scrub up to their elbows before entering the gowning area. NO EXCEPTIONS!&lt;br&gt;- J. Graves</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560899</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Patricia, I hear you're taking my spot tomorrow. Some things to keep in mind.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Be in place by 8:50 AM, simulation time&lt;br&gt;- Don't talk to the subject&lt;br&gt;-Make sure the doors to the backstage are locked.&lt;br&gt;-Don't bother the observation techs, they get cranky after long shifts.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Patricia, I hear you're taking my spot tomorrow. Some things to keep in mind.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Be in place by 8:50 AM, simulation time&lt;br&gt;- Don't talk to the subject&lt;br&gt;- Make sure the doors to the backstage are locked.&lt;br&gt;- Don't bother the observation techs, they get cranky after long shifts.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560901</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Sorry Morgan. Not sure how you managed this, but I can't let you have this keycard. Trust me. You'd regret it. - Alex</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Sorry Morgan. Not sure how you managed this, but I can't let you have this keycard. Trust me. You'd regret it.&lt;br&gt;- Alex</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560903</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">- Recycling charges x3&lt;br&gt;- Wiring&lt;br&gt;- Plastic Tubing&lt;br&gt;- Flask Bourbon x2&lt;br&gt;- Case of Cigars&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;John, I'd take this stuff pretty seriously. I've already alerted Alex to the nature of this contraband. We're taking V-010655-37 out of here. Cigars and booze are one thing, but we can't have volunteers stockpiling stolen recylcer charges. What do you think he plans to do?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Bowser</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">- Recycling charges x3&lt;br&gt;- Wiring&lt;br&gt;- Plastic tubing&lt;br&gt;- Flask bourbon x2&lt;br&gt;- Case of cigars&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;John, I'd take this stuff pretty seriously. I've already alerted Alex to the nature of this contraband. We're taking V-010655-37 out of here. Cigars and booze are one thing, but we can't have volunteers stockpiling stolen recycler charges. What do you think he plans to do?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Bowser</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560907</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wade - PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE with a cherry on top fix the Medical Operator that's been sitting on your desk? &lt;br&gt;-Goldcrest</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Wade - PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE with a cherry on top fix the Medical Operator that's been sitting on your desk?&lt;br&gt;- Goldcrest</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560947</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"> %password% </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">%password%</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560949</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Elias,&lt;br&gt;You left your character sheet on the printer.  Don't forget we moved the game to the rec center in Crew Facilities and it's an hour later than usual.  Do us a favor and take a happy pill before showing up.  See you there.  </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Elias,&lt;br&gt;You left your character sheet on the printer.  Don't forget we moved the game to the rec center in Crew Quarters and it's an hour later than usual. Do us a favor and take a happy pill before showing up. See you there.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887560953</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ms Elazar,&lt;br&gt;I don't know what I saw but I was just trying to do my job. Now I worry I might not get a chance to talk to you so I'm writing this. I don't recall the last time I was scared, but what happened in Sim...&lt;br&gt;I can't get it out of my head.&lt;br&gt;Whatever is happening, I want to help, not sit here in this room. &lt;br&gt;I'm starting to feel like people on station haven't been shooting straight. Like what do they actually do in Psychotronics? No one I talk to goes in there. And Yuri Kimura has un-numbered Neuromods in her office that I thought you should know about. </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Ms Elazar,&lt;br&gt;I don't know what I saw but I was just trying to do my job. Now I worry I might not get a chance to talk to you so I'm writing this. I don't recall the last time I was scared, but what happened in Sim...&lt;br&gt;I can't get it out of my head.&lt;br&gt;Whatever is happening, I want to help, not sit here in this room.&lt;br&gt;I'm starting to feel like people on station haven't been shooting straight. Like what do they actually do in Psychotronics? No one I talk to goes in there. And Yuri Kimura has un-numbered Neuromods in her office that I thought you should know about.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561011</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Todd stowed 3553 before it was completely empty. If you feel like a snack...</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Todd stowed 3553 before it was completely empty. If you feel like having a snack...</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561030</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Food &amp; Supplies</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Food &amp; Supplies</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561031</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">I've gathered all the supplies I could find and it looks like we have enough food to hold out for several days as long as we are rationing. Here is an inventory: &lt;br&gt;3 bananas (use these first, they are going bad) &lt;br&gt;2 pomegranates &lt;br&gt;2 Dim Sum &lt;br&gt;1 Cookie box &lt;br&gt;1 Fish Sticks&lt;br&gt;5 Unagi Rolls &lt;br&gt;3 Udon noodles &lt;br&gt;1 Veggie blend &lt;br&gt;1 Jellied eels (gross) &lt;br&gt;1 Caviar &lt;br&gt;We have all the water we need as long as the fountain  keeps working.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">I've gathered all the supplies I could find and it looks like we have enough food to hold out for several days as long as we are rationing. Here is an inventory: &lt;br&gt;3 bananas (use these first, they are going bad)&lt;br&gt;2 pomegranates&lt;br&gt;2 dim sum&lt;br&gt;1 cookie box &lt;br&gt;1 fish sticks&lt;br&gt;5 unagi rolls&lt;br&gt;3 udon noodles&lt;br&gt;1 veggie blend&lt;br&gt;1 jellied eels (gross)&lt;br&gt;1 caviar&lt;br&gt;We have all the water we need as long as the fountain keeps working.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561049</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Entry 165: I've managed to reduce the growth time to around 10 minutes per fruit. It's remarkable to see them sprout from practically nothing and grow to an edible size and ripeness before my very eyes.&lt;br&gt;More importantly, I finally obtained clearance for wider range testing of the growth formula from Dr. Kelstrup.  All that's left is actually fabricating it, and then inserting it in the sprinkler system. I'm keeping the fabrication plan on my person, as I have no doubt others would love to claim credit for it.&lt;br&gt;- Dr. Julien Howard</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Entry 165: I've managed to reduce the growth time to around 10 minutes per fruit. It's remarkable to see them sprout from practically nothing and grow to an edible size and ripeness before my very eyes.&lt;br&gt;More importantly, I finally obtained clearance for wider range testing of the growth formula from Dr. Kelstrup. All that's left is actually fabricating it, and then inserting it in the sprinkler system. I'm keeping the fabrication plan on my person, as I have no doubt others would love to claim credit for it.&lt;br&gt;- Dr. Julien Howard</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561051</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Julien - Stopped by, but you were out. FYI, reviewed your lab notes. Plants pose no health risk. You should be GTG in Arboretum. -Hans</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Julien - Stopped by, but you were out. FYI, reviewed your lab notes. Plants pose no health risk. You should be GTG in Arboretum.&lt;br&gt;- Hans</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561057</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">IMPORTANT!&lt;br&gt;Log every time you enter the maintenance crawlspace through the access panel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Leaky Pipe (fixed). - R. Wood&lt;br&gt;- Unexplained light flicker. Unable to locate source. Power grid OK. - R. Wood&lt;br&gt;- Electrical device near Machine Shop door unstable. Used local adhesive for temporary fix. - R. Wood.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- *Note* In case of emergency, head into the maintenance crawlspace via the small access panel below to shut off local power. Notify me immediately. - R. Wood</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;Log every time you enter the maintenance crawlspace through the access panel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Leaky Pipe (fixed). R. Wood&lt;br&gt;- Unexplained light flicker. Unable to locate source. Power grid OK. R. Wood&lt;br&gt;- Electrical device near Machine Shop door unstable. Used local adhesive for temporary fix. R. Wood.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- In case of emergency, head into the maintenance crawlspace via the small access panel below to shut off local power. Notify me immediately. R. Wood</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561063</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Subject: Dr. Annalise Gallegos &lt;br&gt;Prepared by: Officer Maliah Fowles &lt;br&gt;For: Alex Yu &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known associate: &lt;b&gt;Quinten Purvis&lt;/b&gt; (Engineer, Life Support) &lt;br&gt;Known associate: &lt;b&gt;William Mitchell&lt;/b&gt; (Chef, Crew Quarters)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;08:05AM     Subject left private quarters. Presumably to report for first shift. Verified with Psychotronics Security.&lt;br&gt;09:13AM     Subject returned to private quarters during shift hours. Reason unknown.&lt;br&gt;09:21AM     Quinten Purvis was observed entering subject's quarters.&lt;br&gt;09:45AM     Quinten Purvis left subject's quarters. Observed carrying a portable drive.&lt;br&gt;10:01AM     Subject left private quarters, walked to cafeteria and was admitted to kitchen by Chef Will Mitchell.&lt;br&gt;10:15AM     Subject left Crew Quarters. Verified with Psychotronics Security subject reported back to workstation.&lt;br&gt;07:47PM     Subject returned to Crew Quarters. Took meal into room.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Subject: Dr. Annalise Gallegos&lt;br&gt;Prepared by: Officer Maliah Fowles&lt;br&gt;For: Alex Yu &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Known associate: &lt;b&gt;Quinten Purvis&lt;/b&gt; (Engineer, Life Support)&lt;br&gt;Known associate: &lt;b&gt;William Mitchell&lt;/b&gt; (Chef, Crew Quarters)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;08:05AM - Subject left private quarters. Presumably to report for first shift. Verified with Psychotronics Security.&lt;br&gt;09:13AM - Subject returned to private quarters during shift hours. Reason unknown.&lt;br&gt;09:21AM - Quinten Purvis was observed entering subject&apos;s quarters.&lt;br&gt;09:45AM - Quinten Purvis left subject&apos;s quarters. Observed carrying a portable drive.&lt;br&gt;10:01AM - Subject left private quarters, walked to cafeteria and was admitted to kitchen by Chef Will Mitchell.&lt;br&gt;10:15AM - Subject left Crew Quarters. Verified with Psychotronics Security subject reported back to workstation.&lt;br&gt;07:47PM - Subject returned to Crew Quarters. Took meal into room.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561075</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Akande&lt;br&gt;Who approved your request for shotgun rounds? We all agree there's something in here, but please don't damage the equip.&lt;br&gt; D. Sho</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Akande&lt;br&gt;Who approved your request for shotgun rounds? We all agree there's something in here, but please don't damage the equip.&lt;br&gt;D. Sho</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561083</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FYI - storage room near the grav shaft has extra 02 tanks. %key%. &lt;br&gt;-Nicole</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">FYI - storage room near the grav shaft has extra O2 tanks. %key%.&lt;br&gt;- Nicole</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561085</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Shut down the grav shafts to keep them from spreading. Utilty on my computer -  tooling room lower level. -Scott</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Shut down the grav shafts to keep them from spreading. Utilty on my computer -  tooling room lower level.&lt;br&gt;- Scott</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561093</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The supervisor authorizing this request certifies that all safety factors have been considered and are satisfactory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department Requesting: Psychotronics&lt;br&gt;Request Prepared by: Dr. Tobias Frost&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AREA OF WORK: &lt;br&gt;Life Support Water Treatment Facility&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORK TO BE DONE: &lt;br&gt;Installment of &lt;b&gt;Psychoactive Particle Injector&lt;/b&gt; (henceforth PPI). I would like to get your approval to connect the PPI to the station water supply. In essence the PPI will alter the composition of drinking water by one part per million by mixing exotic particles at regular intervals. Imbibing the water should positively impact psychoactive potential.&lt;br&gt;Approved by:&lt;u&gt; Dr. Hans Kelstrup&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requires Director Signature?: No&lt;br&gt;DIRECTOR SIGNATURE:&lt;u&gt;&lt;/u&gt;</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The supervisor authorizing this request certifies that all safety factors have been considered and are satisfactory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Department Requesting: Psychotronics&lt;br&gt;Request Prepared by: Dr. Tobias Frost&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AREA OF WORK: &lt;br&gt;Life Support Water Treatment Facility&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;WORK TO BE DONE: &lt;br&gt;Installment of &lt;b&gt;Psychoactive Particle Injector&lt;/b&gt; (henceforth PPI). I would like to get your approval to connect the PPI to the station water supply. In essence the PPI will alter the composition of drinking water by one part per million by mixing exotic particles at regular intervals. Imbibing the water should positively impact psychoactive potential.&lt;br&gt;Approved by: &lt;u&gt;Dr. Hans Kelstrup&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requires Director Signature? No&lt;br&gt;DIRECTOR SIGNATURE:</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561131</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Warning: I've sealed several Mimics inside. Two casualties, so maybe as many as eight Mimics.  -Manion</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Warning: I've sealed several Mimics inside. Two casualties, so maybe as many as eight Mimics.&lt;br&gt;- Manion</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_15373294129887561133</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">-Check phosphate levels of plants in quad 2. &lt;br&gt; -Reduce sprinkler cycle by 5 minutes.&lt;br&gt; -See if Dr. Howard's experimental plants need water. &lt;br&gt; -Dr. Howard changed the greenhouse password to %password%.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">- Check phosphate levels of plants in quad 2.&lt;br&gt;- Reduce sprinkler cycle by 5 minutes.&lt;br&gt;- See if Dr. Howard's experimental plants need water.&lt;br&gt;- Dr. Howard changed the greenhouse password to %password%.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_761057047996407534</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;CONFIDENTIAL PROGRESS REPORT 10B-3&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATTN: William Yu&lt;br&gt;Department: Hardware Labs&lt;br&gt;Project Lead: Lane Carpenter&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;BLACKBOX PROJECT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Q-Beam attachment for N-CN9 &quot;Blackbox&quot; Military Operators is progressing ahead of schedule. Development on outstanding tasks has been broken down below:&lt;br&gt;- Micro-cooling plate optimization: 87% complete&lt;br&gt;- Recirculating ambient control: 70% complete&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you can see, we are nearly there. Once the cooling system has been optimized and migrated into the Q-Beam firing mechanism, prototypes will be sent Earthside. Testing is proceeding as planned. Preliminary results show promising excitations in the molecular structure of energized systems. Live target not yet tested.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;CONFIDENTIAL PROGRESS REPORT 10B-3&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;ATTN: William Yu&lt;br&gt;Department: Hardware Labs&lt;br&gt;Project Lead: Lane Carpenter&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;BLACKBOX PROJECT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Q-Beam attachment for N-CN9 &quot;Blackbox&quot; Military Operators is progressing ahead of schedule. Development on outstanding tasks has been broken down below:&lt;br&gt;- Micro-cooling plate optimization: 87% complete&lt;br&gt;- Recirculating ambient control: 70% complete&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you can see, we are nearly there. Once the cooling system has been optimized and migrated into the Q-Beam firing mechanism, prototypes will be sent Earthside. Testing is proceeding as planned. Preliminary results show promising excitations in the molecular structure of energized systems. Live target not yet tested.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564944031209</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The escape pods didn't work and we believe it was intentional. Those black shapes are everywhere and everyone we know is dead. Or something worse. We aren't going to let that happen to us. To our families, we love you. &lt;br&gt; -Brandi Pester and Jenni Garbentzoff </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">The escape pods didn't work and we believe it was intentional. Those black shapes are everywhere and everyone we know is dead. Or something worse. We aren't going to let that happen to us. To our families, we love you.&lt;br&gt;- Brandi Pester and Jenni Garbentzoff</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_12889009725043563285</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;SUBJECT: &lt;/b&gt;Gustav Leitner&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATE:&lt;/b&gt; [02.13.35]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Results: &lt;/b&gt;Patient tested positive for Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer. Patient did not list any ailments on their submission form prior to being taken to the skill recorder.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact this patient immediately. If patient is still on Talos 1, have him report to the Trauma Center as soon as possible.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;SUBJECT:&lt;/b&gt; Gustav Leitner&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;DATE:&lt;/b&gt; [02.13.35]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Results:&lt;/b&gt; Patient tested positive for Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer. Patient did not list any ailments on their submission form prior to being taken to the skill recorder.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Contact this patient immediately. If patient is still on Talos I, have him report to the Trauma Center as soon as possible.</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564946607740</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Two people have checked out equipment and failed to return it. &lt;br&gt; -Ari Liudnarht &lt;br&gt;-Roger Meir</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Two people have checked out equipment and failed to return it:&lt;br&gt;Ari Liudnarht&lt;br&gt;Roger Meir</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_12889009725044646982</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Luka is no kontrabandist, I don't know why he has the goods that he has. I can show you where he keeps them. But fair is fair. You want his goods, you look other way with me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Evgeni</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Luka is no kontrabandist, I don't know why he has the goods that he has. I can show you where he keeps them. But fair is fair. You want his goods, you look other way with me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Evgeni</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_12889009725044647444</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Drop ceiling outside the door to the habitation pods. -EV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Drop ceiling outside the door to the habitation pods.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- EV</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315648736</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"> Stabfellow's Treasure Map</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Stabfellow's Treasure Map</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417315648784</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"> Rosalyn's Treasure Map</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Rosalyn's Treasure Map</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_4349723564947832225</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;FOUR&lt;/b&gt; Jellied Eels&lt;br&gt;2 Pacific Sliders&lt;br&gt;3 Siskak Unagi Rollz</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">&lt;b&gt;FOUR&lt;/b&gt; jellied eels&lt;br&gt;2 pacific sliders&lt;br&gt;3 unagi rolls</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_418270515491521615</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Annie,&lt;br&gt;I know you'll never read this. I ran out of my office when I heard you screaming, but there were just too many of them between me and you. You were always really nice to me. You didn't deserve to die like that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And now they're in my office, and I'm surrounded out here in this cage. I can't help myself, much less you, or even Mia. Even when I try, I still screw things up. I'm sorry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Scott</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Annie,&lt;br&gt;I know you'll never read this. I ran out of my office when I heard you screaming, but there were just too many of them between me and you. You were always really nice to me. You didn't deserve to die like that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And now they're in my office, and I'm surrounded out here in this cage. I can't help myself, much less you, or even Mia. Even when I try, I still screw things up. I'm sorry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Scott</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_844024417316345124</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We locked the doors to the greenhouse but this one flies! We don't have long before it figures out the roof isn't covered. 5 min ago Edna tried making it into the greenhouse before it took her over. She won't stop screaming. Yelling at us to stay back. If we can kill the floating thing that infected her maybe we can save her. If you find this note please help. Kill it because we won't be ourselves.&lt;br&gt;-Rani </Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">We locked the doors to the greenhouse but this one flies! We don't have long before it figures out the roof isn't covered. 5 min ago Edna tried making it into the greenhouse before it took her over. She won't stop screaming. Yelling at us to stay back. If we can kill the floating thing that infected her maybe we can save her. If you find this note please help. Kill it because we won't be ourselves.&lt;br&gt;- Rani</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263414434929</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Door actuators are wonky. Come see me if you need in. &lt;br&gt;-Graves</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">Door actuators are wonky. Come see me if you need in.&lt;br&gt;- Graves</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
   <Row ss:AutoFitHeight="0">
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">loc_13680621263415321367</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a Readme.txt file found on Annalise Gallegos' thumb drive.]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drive in your possession contains incriminating evidence related to illegal experiments performed aboard Talos I in the Psychotronics labs. This includes, but is not limited to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;» Classified internal memorandums.&lt;br&gt;» Key research data, spanning several decades.&lt;br&gt;» Names and roles of all personnel involved.&lt;br&gt;» Volunteer ID's matched with their real names.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This information will corroborate the existence of an extra-terrestrial species (called Typhon) as well as the fact that all Neuromods are made at the expense of human victims. I harbor no illusions that this will be easy to believe, but I can testify to its veracity – assuming I am still alive - because I was a participant in many of the experiments referenced.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Dr. Annalise Gallegos</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">[Excerpt from a Readme.txt file found on Annalise Gallegos&apos; thumb drive]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The drive in your possession contains incriminating evidence related to illegal experiments performed aboard Talos I in the Psychotronics labs. This includes, but is not limited to:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;» Classified internal memorandums&lt;br&gt;» Key research data, spanning several decades&lt;br&gt;» Names and roles of all personnel involved&lt;br&gt;» Volunteer IDs matched with their real names&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This information will corroborate the existence of an extra-terrestrial species (called Typhon) as well as the fact that all Neuromods are made at the expense of human victims. I harbor no illusions that this will be easy to believe, but I can testify to its veracity – assuming I am still alive - because I was a participant in many of the experiments referenced.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Dr. Annalise Gallegos</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String">LOCKED</Data></Cell>
    <Cell><Data ss:Type="String"></Data></Cell>
   </Row>
  </Table>
  <WorksheetOptions xmlns="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:excel">
   <Unsynced/>
   <Selected/>
   <TopRowVisible>175</TopRowVisible>
   <Panes>
    <Pane>
     <Number>3</Number>
     <ActiveRow>196</ActiveRow>
     <ActiveCol>1</ActiveCol>
    </Pane>
   </Panes>
   <ProtectObjects>False</ProtectObjects>
   <ProtectScenarios>False</ProtectScenarios>
  </WorksheetOptions>
 </Worksheet>
 <x:ExcelWorkbook/>
</Workbook>
